import type { QuestionOptions } from './interfaces'

export const questions: QuestionOptions[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: '17 rounded off to the nearest 10 is.',
    answer: '20',
    options: {
      a: '10',
      b: '20',
      c: '17'
    }
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: '75 rounded off to the nearest 10 is.',
    answer: '80',
    options: {
      a: '70',
      b: '80',
      c: '175'
    }
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: '64 rounded off to the nearest 10 is.',
    answer: '70',
    options: {
      a: '64',
      b: '70',
      c: '60'
    }
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: '98 rounded off to the nearest 10 is.',
    answer: '100',
    options: {
      a: '80',
      b: '100',
      c: '89'
    }
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: '94 rounded off to the nearest 10 is.',
    answer: '100',
    options: {
      a: '100',
      b: '94',
      c: '90'
    }
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: '445 rounded off to the nearest 10 is.',
    answer: '450',
    options: {
      a: '450',
      b: '440',
      c: '500'
    }
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: '45 rounded off to the nearest 10 is.',
    answer: '50',
    options: {
      a: '50',
      b: '45',
      c: '40'
    }
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: '999 rounded off to the nearest 10 is.',
    answer: '1000',
    options: {
      a: '990',
      b: '1000',
      c: '909'
    }
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: '165 rounded off to the nearest 10 is.',
    answer: '170',
    options: {
      a: '160',
      b: '170',
      c: '150'
    }
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: '19 rounded off to the nearest 10 is.',
    answer: '20',
    options: {
      a: '20',
      b: '10',
      c: '19'
    }
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: '0 rounded off to the nearest 10 is.',
    answer: '0',
    options: {
      a: '10',
      b: '1',
      c: '0'
    }
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: '199 rounded off to the nearest 10 is.',
    answer: '200',
    options: {
      a: '190',
      b: '100',
      c: '200'
    }
  }
]
